<Brothers>
	<Brother>
		<Position>Master Alchemist</Position>
		<FirstName>Daniel</FirstName>
		<LastName>Verrico</LastName>
		<Major>Chemistry</Major>
		<Class>2018</Class>
		<PledgeYear>Fall '15</PledgeYear>
		<Email>mabetasigma@gmail.com</Email>
		<Bio>
			cryingdan.jpg
		</Bio>
	</Brother>
	<Brother>
		<Position>Vice-Master Alchemist</Position>
		<FirstName>William</FirstName>
		<LastName>Charbonneau</LastName>
		<Major>Chemistry</Major>
		<Class>2019</Class>
		<PledgeYear>Spring '17</PledgeYear>
		<Email>vmabetasigma@gmail.com</Email>
		<Bio>
			Will has a nice ponytail
		</Bio>
	</Brother>
	<Brother>
		<Position>Master of Ceremonies</Position>
		<FirstName>Kevin</FirstName>
		<LastName>Hernandez</LastName>
		<Major>Chemistry</Major>
		<Class>2019</Class>
		<PledgeYear>Spring '16</PledgeYear>
		<Email>mcbetasigma@gmail.com</Email>
		<Bio>
			Kev doesn't care. 
		</Bio>
	</Brother>
	<Brother>
		<Position>Treasurer</Position>
		<FirstName>Samantha</FirstName>
		<LastName>Burger</LastName>
		<Major>Biochemistry</Major>
		<Class>2020</Class>
		<PledgeYear>Fall '17</PledgeYear>
		<Email>treasurybetasigma@gmail.com</Email>
		<Bio>
			Sam is from a small town in New York. She is very glad to be here at RIT and to be a brother of Alpha Chi Sigma.			
		</Bio>
	</Brother>
	<Brother>
		<Position>Reporter &amp; Social Chair</Position>
		<FirstName>Alexis</FirstName>
		<LastName>Slenz</LastName>
		<Major>Chemistry</Major>
		<Class>2019</Class>
		<PledgeYear>Spring '18</PledgeYear>
		<Email>n/a</Email>
		<Bio>
			Lexie is a fourth year chemistry student with a focus in environmental science and a minor in language science.  She is currently the Reporter and social committee chair of the Beta Sigma chapter.  Outside of AXS Lexie is very involved on RIT’s campus; she is a dancer and former E-Board member of the Vis Viva Dance Company, is a College if Science Student Ambassador, an eager volunteer for the School of Chemistry and Material Science, and has also been a lab teaching assistant and Orientation Leader in the past.  After RIT she hopes to pursue a geosciences career in glaciology and paleoclimatology.
		</Bio>
	</Brother>
	<Brother>
		<Position>Recorder</Position>
		<FirstName>Eliot</FirstName>
		<LastName>Patnode</LastName>
		<Major>Chemical Engineering</Major>
		<Class>2019</Class>
		<PledgeYear>Fall '15</PledgeYear>
		<Email>n/a</Email>
		<Bio>
			Eliot is devoid of all attributes due to an unfortunate curse.
		</Bio>
	</Brother>
		<Brother>
		<Position>Professional Chair</Position>
		<FirstName>Jordan</FirstName>
		<LastName>Dejewski</LastName>
		<Major>Biochemistry</Major>
		<Class></Class>
		<PledgeYear>Spring '18</PledgeYear>
		<Email>n/a</Email>
		<Bio>
			
		</Bio>
	</Brother>
	<Brother>
		<Position>Community Service Chair</Position>
		<FirstName>Peyton</FirstName>
		<LastName>Kunselman</LastName>
		<Major>Chemistry</Major>
		<Class>2020</Class>
		<PledgeYear>Spring '18</PledgeYear>
		<Email>n/a</Email>
		<Bio>
			Hello, my name is Peyton Kunselman. I am going into my second year here at RIT. I am a Chemistry major. I pledged last semester (Spring 18). I am the new community service chair. I am currently doing research with Dr. Eddingsaas focusing on the production of Aldehydes from E-Cigarettes and Hookah. Before that, I worked on one of Dr. Craig’s projects. Other than school work, I really love to play guitar and to play video games.
		</Bio>
	</Brother>
	<Brother>
		<Position>Historian</Position>
		<FirstName>Joseph</FirstName>
		<LastName>Discua</LastName>
		<Major>Biochemistry</Major>
		<Class>2019</Class>
		<PledgeYear>Spring '18</PledgeYear>
		<Email>n/a</Email>
		<Bio>
			Hi! My name is Joe Discua. I’m a 5th year biochemistry major and from New Hampshire. I like long walks on the Gracie’s trail and have become a sommelier of different sodas from various vending machines. I’m from New Hampshire and enjoy hiking the presidential mountain range and exploring the wilderness. I came to RIT for the biochemistry program but stayed for the friends.
		</Bio>
	</Brother>
	<Brother>
		<Position>Public Relations Chair</Position>
		<FirstName>Hannah</FirstName>
		<LastName>Thompson</LastName>
		<Big>Kevin Hernandez</Big>
		<Major>Biomedical Engineering BS and Science Technology and Public Policy MS</Major>
		<Class>2020</Class>
		<PledgeYear>Spring '18</PledgeYear>
		<Email>n/a</Email>
		<Bio>
			My name is Hannah Thompson and I’m a rising 4th year studying Biomedical Engineering. I am part of a BS/MS program working towards a Masters in Science, Technology and Public Policy with an environmental focus. I hope to combine my technical knowledge with environmental awareness and consideration in my future career. I pledged the fraternity during the Spring of 2018. I’ve recently become the Public Relations Chair which I’m extremely excited about. I want to work to increase our presence on campus and develop more direct ways to connect with the community and potential members.
		</Bio>
	</Brother>
	<Brother>
		<Position>Cyber Alchemist</Position>
		<FirstName>Joshua</FirstName>
		<LastName>Evans</LastName>
		<Big>Dana Soika</Big>
		<Major>Biotechonology and Molecular Bioscience</Major>
		<Class>2020</Class>
		<PledgeYear>Spring '18</PledgeYear>
		<Email>webmasterbetasigma@gmail.com</Email>
		<Bio>
			I am a fourth year at RIT, but I’ve only been here for two years and probably won’t graduate for at least one more.  My area of interest is Genetic Engineering, and my life’s goal is to become a character in a Michael Crichton novel. I am involved in a research project on plant hormones with Dr. Coleman and Dr. Hudson, as well as a protein dynamics project with Dr. Babbit.  I decided to pledge after I attended an info session for free pizza with no plans on actually joining, and it kind of got away from me. I love the friendly, intellectual, but fun atmosphere of Alpha Chi Sigma and am enjoying my first semester as a Brother.
		</Bio>
	</Brother>
	<Brother>
		<Position>Inactive</Position>
		<FirstName>Megan</FirstName>
		<LastName>Owens</LastName>
		<Major>Chemical Engineering</Major>
		<Class>2019</Class>
		<PledgeYear>Fall '15</PledgeYear>
		<Email>n/a</Email>
		<Bio>
			I am a fifth year chemical engineering student who joined during my second year at RIT. After graduation, I will be going to grad school or taking on a full time job....to be decided! Alpha Chi Sigma has been where most of my time outside of classes has been. It has given me some of the best friends and best memories I could have at RIT! Apart from studying and the fraternity, I spend msot of my time with my dog Bailey or reading a good sci-fi book. 
		</Bio>
	</Brother>
	<Brother>
		<Position>Inactive</Position>
		<FirstName>John</FirstName>
		<LastName>Ste. Marie</LastName>
		<Major>Chemical Engineering</Major>
		<Class></Class>
		<PledgeYear>Spring '16</PledgeYear>
		<Email>n/a</Email>
		<Bio>
			
		</Bio>
	</Brother>
	<Brother>
		<Position>Inctive</Position>
		<FirstName>Joseph</FirstName>
		<LastName>Hunt</LastName>
		<Major>Chemical Engineering</Major>
		<Class>2019</Class>
		<PledgeYear>Spring '16</PledgeYear>
		<Bio>
			
		</Bio>
	</Brother>
	<Brother>
		<Position>Inactive</Position>
		<FirstName>Trent</FirstName>
		<LastName>Mochel</LastName>
		<Big>David Tolge</Big>
		<Major>Chemistry</Major>
		<Class></Class>
		<PledgeYear>Fall '16</PledgeYear>
		<Bio>
			
		</Bio>
	</Brother>
	<Brother>
		<Position>Inactive</Position>
		<FirstName>David</FirstName>
		<LastName>Tolge</LastName>
		<Big></Big>
		<Major></Major>
		<Class>Unknown?</Class>
		<PledgeYear></PledgeYear>
		<Bio></Bio>
	<Brother>
		<Position>Active</Position>
		<FirstName>Matthew</FirstName>
		<LastName>Bonney</LastName>
		<Major>Chemistry</Major>
		<Class></Class>
		<PledgeYear>Fall '16</PledgeYear>
		<Bio>
			I am from a small town in the southern tier called Greene, NY. This is my fourth and final year at RIT, and I’ve enjoyed my time immensely, especially with AXS. It's a constructive enviroment and like minded nerds striving for greatness in the field of science. I enjoy reading, solving puzzles, coming up with weird ciphers, watching all sorts of interesting shows; anime, music, and theater. Outside of AXS, I’m in some other cool organizations like Computer Science House, which is always up to some weird antics. After RIT I plan to continue my education at grad school with the aim of a PhD in physical chemistry.  

		</Bio>
	</Brother>
	<Brother>
		<Position>Active</Position>
		<FirstName>Dennis</FirstName>
		<LastName>Bogdan</LastName>
		<Major>Chemical Engineering</Major>
		<Class></Class>
		<PledgeYear>Spring '17</PledgeYear>
		<Bio>
			I am a 3rd year Chemical Engineering major here at RIT. I hail from the town of Broadalbin, NY located in the southern portion of the Adirondack Mountains. I became a brother of Alpha Chi Sigma in the Spring of 2017. Here on campus I am a member of the 2018 Division II National Champion Roller Hockey Team. After RIT I plan to apply my studies to the brewing or metallurgy industries. Some of my hobbies include blacksmithing, hockey, running and playing squash.
		</Bio>
	</Brother>
	<Brother>
		<Position>Active</Position>
		<FirstName>Hannah</FirstName>
		<LastName>Sheldon</LastName>
		<Big>Megan Owens</Big>
		<Major>Biochemistry</Major>
		<Class></Class>
		<PledgeYear>Spring '17</PledgeYear>
		<Bio>
			I’m a third(ish) year biochemistry major with aspirations to become a pharmacist after I pass orgo II. I pledged second semester of my freshman year and secretly have the best family tree. Variety is the spice of life.
		</Bio>
	</Brother>
	<Brother>
		<Position>Active</Position>
		<FirstName>Luke</FirstName>
		<LastName>Lanza</LastName>
		<Major>Chemistry</Major>
		<Class></Class>
		<PledgeYear>Spring '17</PledgeYear>
		<Bio>
			I am a 4th year chemistry major from Buffalo NY. I do not currently hold any position in the fraternity as my final year of undergraduate studies keeps me quite busy. I pledged Alpha Chi Sigma in the fall of 2017 and I have enjoyed my time immensley and am very glad I joined, the freinds and connections iv'e made through this organisation are something i will always be thankful for. Upon graduating in the fall with a minor in biology i hope to apply my trade in the industry doing organic synthesis before going back to school to obtain my masters.
		</Bio>
	</Brother>
	<Brother>
		<Position>Inactive</Position>
		<FirstName>Dana</FirstName>
		<LastName>Soika</LastName>
		<Major>Biotechnology and Molecular Bioscience</Major>
		<Class></Class>
		<PledgeYear>Fall '17</PledgeYear>
		<Bio>
			
		</Bio>
	</Brother>
	<Brother>
		<Position>Active</Position>
		<FirstName>Alexander</FirstName>
		<LastName>North</LastName>
		<Major>Chemistry</Major>
		<Class></Class>
		<PledgeYear>Spring '18</PledgeYear>
		<Bio>
			I am a fifth year undergraduate chemistry major who became a brother in spring of 2018. I am involved in a renewable polymer research lab with Dr. Miri.I hail from Westminster, MD. I have very much enjoyed my time here in the chapter, and am excited to see what it becomes. After RIT I plan on taking a break from school before pursing a graduate degree.
		</Bio>
	</Brother>
	<Brother>
		<Position>Active</Position>
		<FirstName>Tullio</FirstName>
		<LastName>Geraci</LastName>
		<Major>Chemistry</Major>
		<Class></Class>
		<PledgeYear>Spring '18</PledgeYear>
		<Bio>
			Tullio is a fourth year chemistry major working on minors in Mathematics and American Sign Language &amp; Deaf Culture Studies. Outside of pledging for Alpha Chi Sigma, he is very involved on campus; he is the treasurer of STAR (Space-Time Adventures at RIT), RIT’s Sci-fi Club as well as being the treasurer of the RIT Chapter of the American Chemical Society. He is currently between research groups, but in the past he has work with Dr. Matt Miri on fully renewable, plant based plastics, and Dr. Scott Williams on high energy radiation detectors. After RIT he plans to pursue a graduate degree and career in Astrochemistry.
		</Bio>
	</Brother>
	<Brother>
		<Position>Inctive</Position>
		<FirstName>Nathan</FirstName>
		<LastName>Johnson</LastName>
		<Major>Chemistry</Major>
		<Class></Class>
		<PledgeYear>Spring '18</PledgeYear>
		<Bio>
			Nathan is a fourth-year chemistry student with a minor in mathematics, and this is his third year at RIT. He enjoys working on Dr. Coleman’s chiral N-heterocyclic carbene project and is grateful to be surrounded by plenty of other people passionate about chemistry and related fields. He plans to pursue a chemistry PhD after leaving RIT.
		</Bio>
	</Brother>
	<Brother>
		<Position>Inactive</Position>
		<FirstName>Hira</FirstName>
		<LastName>Abid</LastName>
		<Major>Chemical Engineering</Major>
		<Class></Class>
		<PledgeYear>Spring '18</PledgeYear>
		<Bio>
			Hi! I’m a rising third year student from Miami, Florida.  I’m currently working as a Co-op at Regeneron Pharmaceuticals in the Preclinical Manufacturing and Process Development department.
		</Bio>
	</Brother>
	<Brother>
		<Position>Active</Position>
		<FirstName>Jared</FirstName>
		<LastName>Ponzetti</LastName>
		<Major>Software Engineering</Major>
		<Class></Class>
		<PledgeYear>Spring '18</PledgeYear>
		<Bio>
			I am a second-year software engineer. I really like chemistry and I am planning to do at least a minor in chemistry. I hope to one day find a job which involves both software engineering and chemistry.
		</Bio>
	</Brother>
	<Brother>
		<Position>Active</Position>
		<FirstName>Aubrey</FirstName>
		<LastName>Holland</LastName>
		<Major>Chemistry</Major>
		<Class></Class>
		<PledgeYear>Spring '18</PledgeYear>
		<Bio>
			I am a second-year chemistry major, and I am minoring in environmental studies. I come all the way from Olathe, Kansas, but after a year at RIT, I can't imagine going to school anywhere else. Chemistry and environmental efforts are definitely my life, but in my free time I enjoy collecting vinyl, watching and quoting movies, drinking coffee, and being outside.
		</Bio>
	</Brother>
	<Brother>
		<Position>Active</Position>
		<FirstName>Sean</FirstName>
		<LastName>Su</LastName>
		<Major>Chemical Engineering</Major>
		<Class>7</Class>
		<PledgeYear>Spring '18</PledgeYear>
		<Bio>
			Resident mad scientist (2 of 6).
		</Bio>
	</Brother>
	<Brother>
		<Position>Active</Position>
		<FirstName>Andrew</FirstName>
		<LastName>Morris</LastName>
		<Big>Aubrey Holland</Big>
		<Major>2022</Major>
		<Class>Chemical Engineering</Class>
		<PledgeYear>Fall '18</PledgeYear>
		<Bio></Bio>
	</Brother>
	<Brother>
		<Position>Active</Position>
		<FirstName>Rob</FirstName>
		<LastName>Winter</LastName>
		<Major></Major>
		<Class></Class>
		<PledgeYear>Fall '18</PledgeYear>
		<Email>n/a</Email>
		<Bio></Bio>
	</Brother>
	<Brother>
		<Position>Active</Position>
		<FirstName>Izzy</FirstName>
		<LastName>Updike</LastName>
		<Big>Matthew Bonney</Big>
		<Major>Chemical Engineering</Major>
		<Class>2021</Class>
		<PledgeYear>Fall '18</PledgeYear>
		<Bio></Bio>
	</Brother>
	<Brother>
		<Position>Active</Position>
		<FirstName>Victoria</FirstName>
		<LastName>Adams</LastName>
		<Big>Samantha Burger</Big>
		<Major>2022</Major>
		<Class>Chemical Engineering</Class>
		<PledgeYear>Fall '18</PledgeYear>
		<Bio></Bio>
	</Brother>
	<Brother>
		<Position>Active</Position>
		<FirstName>Micah</FirstName>
		<LastName>Sidorick</LastName>
		<Major>Chemical Engineering</Major>
		<Class>2022</Class>
		<PledgeYear>Fall '18</PledgeYear>
		<Bio></Bio>
	</Brother>
	<Brother>
		<Position>Active</Position>
		<FirstName>Denise</FirstName>
		<LastName>Grimon</LastName>
		<Major>2021</Major>
		<Class>Chemistry</Class>
		<PledgeYear>Fall '18</PledgeYear>
		<Bio></Bio>
	</Brother>
	<Brother>
		<Position>Active</Position>
		<FirstName>Lili</FirstName>
		<LastName>Shelby</LastName>
		<Big>Alexis Slenz</Big>
		<Major>2021</Major>
		<Class>Chemistry</Class>
		<PledgeYear>Fall '18</PledgeYear>
		<Bio></Bio>
	</Brother>
	<Brother>
		<Position>Active</Position>
		<FirstName>Colin</FirstName>
		<LastName>Pierce</LastName>
		<Big>Jordan Dejewski</Big>
		<Major>2022</Major>
		<Class>Chemical Engineering</Class>
		<PledgeYear>Fall '18</PledgeYear>
		<Bio></Bio>
	</Brother>
	<Brother>
		<Position>Active</Position>
		<FirstName>Jordan</FirstName>
		<LastName>McNaughton</LastName>
		<Major></Major>
		<Class></Class>
		<PledgeYear>Fall '18</PledgeYear>
		<Bio></Bio>
	</Brother>
	<Brother>
		<Position>Active</Position>
		<FirstName>Jaser</FirstName>
		<LastName>Iniguez</LastName>
		<Big>Jared Ponzetti</Big>
		<Major></Major>
		<Class></Class>
		<PledgeYear>Fall '18</PledgeYear>
		<Bio></Bio>
	</Brother>
	<Brother>
		<Position>Alum</Position>
		<FirstName>Dan</FirstName>
		<LastName>Saviola</LastName>
		<Major>Chemistry</Major>
		<Class></Class>
		<PledgeYear></PledgeYear>
		<Bio>
		</Bio>
	</Brother>
</Brothers>